<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Compilations on Hassan&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.example.com/compilations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Compilations on Hassan&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2020 Hassan. </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 11:36:33 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.example.com/compilations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogs</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/compilations/blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 11:36:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/compilations/blogs/</guid>
      <description>Here are compilations from other blogs which I found really valuable. Bill Gurley: Blogs.
Eric Lefkofsky:Blogs.Marc Suster:Blogs.Naval Ravikant:Blogs.Reid Hoffman:Blogs.Tom Glocer:Blogs.Vinod Khosla:Blogs.Connect with me on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Vision</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/compilations/computer-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 11:36:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/compilations/computer-vision/</guid>
      <description>Here are some papers which every computer vision enthusiast should look into:
 Learning Depth with Convolutional Spatial Propagation Network (link) Stacked Hourglass Networks for Human Pose Estimation (link) Volumetric Regression Networks for 3D Human Body Reconstruction (link) Speed Estimation w/ 3D Object Detection (link) EfficientNet: Rethinking Model Scaling for Convolutional Neural Networks (link) MobileNetV2: Inverted Residuals and Linear Bottlenecks (link) OpenPose: Realtime Multi-Person 2D Pose Estimation using Part Affinity Fields (link) Dynamic Routing Between Capsules (link) Atlas: End-to-End 3D Scene Reconstruction from Posed Images (link)  Other curated compilations of papers for further reading (computer vision and deep learning in general):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/compilations/natural-language-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 11:36:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/compilations/natural-language-processing/</guid>
      <description>Here are some papers which every computer vision enthusiast should look into:
 Attention is all You Need (link) Adversarial Training Methods for Semi-Supervised Text Classification (link) DistilBERT, a distilled version of BERT: smaller, faster, cheaper and lighter (link) Deep contextualized word representations (link) Incorporating BERT into Neural Machine Translation (link) Unsupervised Statistical Machine Translation (link) DialogueGCN: A Graph Convolutional Neural Network for Emotion Recognition in Conversation (link) DialogueRNN: An Attentive RNN for Emotion Detection in Conversations (link)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Computing</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/compilations/quantum-computing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 11:36:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/compilations/quantum-computing/</guid>
      <description>Here are some compilations of posts from blogs which I find really valuable.
 Continuous-variable quantum neural networks (link) Quantum Natural Gradient (link) Transfer learning in hybrid classical-quantum neural networks (link) Variational Quantum Circuits for Deep Reinforcement Learning (link)  Other curated compilations of quantum papers for further reading:
 Really Interesting Set of Medium Blogs on Quantum (link) More Resources on Quantum (link)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://www.example.com/compilations/reinforcement-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 11:36:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.example.com/compilations/reinforcement-learning/</guid>
      <description>Here are some papers which every computer vision enthusiast should look into:
 Capturing Financial markets to apply Deep Reinforcement Learning (link) A Brief Survey of Deep Reinforcement Learning (link) Deep Reinforcement Learning with Double Q-learning (link) HATS: A Hierarchical Graph Attention Network for Stock Movement Prediction (link)  Other curated lists of RL papers for further reading:
 OpenAI Compilation (link) TopBot Compilation + Summaries (link) Robert T Blog: Papers + SUmmaries (link) Best Deep Reinforcement Learning Research of 2019 So Far (link) MC reinforcement learning paper compilations (link) Neptune AI paper compilation (link)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>